{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877418615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877418615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877419126","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877419125"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877425186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877425186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877425708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877425708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877431905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877431905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877432649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877432649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877435453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877435453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" va"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877436410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877436410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877442437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877442437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877443745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877443745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" va"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877449781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877449781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" va"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877455748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877455748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" va"," userResponse":" va"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877456526","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877456526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877462468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877462468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877463306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877463306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877468908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877468908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877474789","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877474789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877475140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877475140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877475961","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877475961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877476602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877476602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877479648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877479647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877480518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877480518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877486768","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877486768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877492942","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877492942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877494763","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877494763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877495780","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877495780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877501997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877501997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877503100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877503100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mu"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877506522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877506522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877507993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877507993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877514370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877514370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877520365","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877520365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877521494","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877521493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877522460","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877522460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877528361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877528360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877529259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877529258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877532527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877532527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877533158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877533158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877539196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877539196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877545114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877545114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877550973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877550973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877552033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877552033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877557798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877557798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877558448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877558448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877564272","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877564272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877565153","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877565153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877568936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877568935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877575169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877575169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877581345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877581344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877582567","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877582567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877588640","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877588640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877589709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877589709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877595782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877595782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877596843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877596842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877600447","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877600447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877600922","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877600922"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877606944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877606944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877607491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877607491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877613659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877613658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877614625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877614625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877618347","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877618347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877624197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877624196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877630227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877630227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877631202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877631202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877632813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877632813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" so"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877633734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877633734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877639784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877639784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877646171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877646171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877652432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877652432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877658813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877658813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877660731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877660731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877670337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877670337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877672339","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877672339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877673707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877673707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877674398","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877674398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877677043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877677042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" fb8f217b-72c3-462d-b32d-6b6647617f1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877689496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877689495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877689731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877689730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877690711","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877690710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877692000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877691999"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877694915","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877694914"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877695770","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877695769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877696090","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877696090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877697341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877697341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877700898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877700898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877701896","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877701896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877702161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877702161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877703120","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877703120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877706048","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877706048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877707091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877707091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877707574","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877707574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877712125","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877712124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877712229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877712229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" b63fec34-70a7-429c-a54c-392233205015"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877729451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877729451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877732454","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877732454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877734396","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877734396"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877740108","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877740108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877741169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877741169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877746005","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877746005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877748185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877748185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877749674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877749674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877750554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877750553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877756168","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877756167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877757973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877757972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877758945","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877758945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877759835","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877759835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877764397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877764397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877766182","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877766182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877767834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877767834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" che"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877768655","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877768655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877773140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877773140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877775065","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877775064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877776537","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877776536"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877777732","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877777732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877782268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877782267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877792696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877792696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877794630","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877794630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877796314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877796314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877797203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877797203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877805185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877805185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877806864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877806864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877808524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877808523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877809755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877809755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877815692","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877815692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877816803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877816803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877820759","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877820759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877822230","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877822229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877823923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877823923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877825008","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877825008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877829827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877829826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877831187","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877831187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877832334","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877832333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877838439","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877838439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877840407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877840407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877846526","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877846526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877849880","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877849879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877855832","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877855832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877857389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877857389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" che"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877858245","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877858244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877860234","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877860233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 97de2d84-7cdd-4bea-a468-7f5018183fad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877882209","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877882209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877891606","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877891606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877899229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877899229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877905992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877905992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877914550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877914550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-10-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877922491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877922491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877930560","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877930560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-13"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877949178","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877949178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877959417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877959417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877969699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877969699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877982752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877982752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549877989465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549877989464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 8321034e-1de4-4550-a37a-a138740e1057"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878000508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878000507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878002528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878002527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878010471","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878010471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878012679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878012678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878023213","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878023213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878025140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878025139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878026697","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878026696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878027144","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878027143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878027350","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878027350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878027860","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878027859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878039115","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878039115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878040915","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878040915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878045163","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878045163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878053868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878053868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878056857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878056856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878059009","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878059008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" NINASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878059596","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878059595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878059794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878059793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878060557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878060557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878064693","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878064693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878066785","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878066785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878068672","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878068672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878069445","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878069445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878072884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878072883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878074929","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878074929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878076613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878076613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878080211","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878080211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878081989","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878081989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878083222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878083221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" NIMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878083665","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878083664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878084427","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878084427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" MSTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878088191","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878088191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878091153","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878091151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878094942","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878094942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878096806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878096806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878098261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878098261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANANIIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878098718","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878098717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878104692","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878104692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878107253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878107253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878109158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878109157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878110888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878110888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878113060","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878113060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878114790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878114790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878115144","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878115144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878116097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878116097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878116581","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878116581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878117453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878117453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" HUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878120811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878120811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878122955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878122955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878126749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878126749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878127847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878127846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878129767","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878129767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878131682","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878131681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TWASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878132545","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878132545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878133223","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878133223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878134310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878134310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878137079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878137079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878138203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878138203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYE"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878139943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878139943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYE"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878141678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878141678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878144369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878144369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" START_MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878151468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878151467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878154268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878154268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878159607","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878159607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878161266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878161266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878163374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878163374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878165444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878165444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878165916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878165916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYE"," userResponse":" ALIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878166519","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878166519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878167082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878167082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878168405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878168405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" ANAWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878168795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878168795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878169502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878169501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878184322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878184322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATAGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878186582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878186581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878188620","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878188620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878189622","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878189622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878191244","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878191244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878191539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878191539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALE"," userResponse":" START_WATATAGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878193142","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878193142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878195126","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878195126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATAGA"," userResponse":" WATATAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878195922","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878195921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYAI"," userResponse":" MAYAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878196536","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878196536"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878196879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878196879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALE"," userResponse":" ALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878200791","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878200790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878202824","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878202824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878205959","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878205959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878208959","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878208958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878211321","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878211321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878212843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878212842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878214247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878214246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878218611","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878218610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878220616","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878220615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878221316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878221316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878222444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878222444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUDI"," userResponse":" WANARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878223215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878223214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878223767","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878223767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878225469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878225469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878228006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878228005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_WANATABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878230006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878230006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878232840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878232839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" WANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878235725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878235724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASIKIA"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878237379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878237378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASIKIA"," userResponse":" NAWASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878239456","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878239456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIIMBA"," userResponse":" WAKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878241260","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878241260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878245698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878245698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878245827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878245826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878250987","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878250986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 9587917a-7e4d-4746-af11-63026cf53fe5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878264132","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878264132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878265288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878265288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878271395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878271395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878272003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878272003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878273656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878273656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878280827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878280827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878285200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878285199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878286877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878286877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878293020","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878293020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878293765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878293765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ke"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878299630","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878299630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878301127","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878301126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878307405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878307405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878313968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878313968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878315374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878315374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878316579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878316579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ge"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878326361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878326361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878329305","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878329305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878332899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878332899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878333666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878333666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878341070","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878341070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878347921","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878347921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878351364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878351364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878352604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878352604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" che"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878353629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878353629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878359268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878359268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878366045","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878366045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878367802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878367801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878369596","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878369596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878370597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878370597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mu"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878377949","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878377949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878384390","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878384390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878385340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878385340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878388824","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878388824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878389550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878389550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878395935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878395935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878396771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878396771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878402881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878402881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878403925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878403925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878404687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878404687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878410354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878410353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878416375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878416375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878422424","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878422424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878423195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878423194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878429424","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878429424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878436484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878436483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878437457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878437457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" so"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878437885","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878437885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878443321","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878443321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878446692","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878446692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878455907","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878455907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878457909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878457909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878458848","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878458848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878461895","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878461895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878464866","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878464866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 5ef939a5-aff8-499a-9449-23cf5de4a796"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878481655","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878481655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878499014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878499014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-15"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878506041","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878506041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-15"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878511903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878511903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-15"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878518970","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878518970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_16-10-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878525501","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878525501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_16-10-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878532808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878532808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_11-6-14"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878538296","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878538296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-5-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878544660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878544660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-15-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878550886","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878550885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878556383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878556382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-6-14"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878563423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878563423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-3-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878572173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878572173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-15"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878578843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878578842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" ef173e2d-c543-4945-9188-83e7b602c629"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-15"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878594021","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878594021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878604469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878604468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878605701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878605701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878606349","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878606349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878606957","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878606956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878611510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878611510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878612082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878612082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878613316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878613316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878614144","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878614144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878614580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878614580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878619195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878619195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878620829","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878620829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878621716","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878621716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878622512","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878622512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ke"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878626818","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878626818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878627526","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878627526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878628210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878628210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878628715","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878628715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878633686","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878633686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878634473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878634473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878635132","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878635132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878635577","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878635577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878639898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878639898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwa"," userResponse":" mwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878640582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878640582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878641318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878641318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878641968","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878641968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nzi"," userResponse":" nzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878646802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878646802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878647623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878647623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878648316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878648316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878649052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878649052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878653366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878653366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878655087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878655086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878655845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878655845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878662331","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878662331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878663255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878663255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878669518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878669518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878669971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878669971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878674934","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878674934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878676063","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878676063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878677383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878677383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878678599","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878678598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878680267","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878680267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878685939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878685939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878686690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878686690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" va"," userResponse":" va"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878687383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878687383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878687974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878687974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878690088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878690087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_123000"," gameId":" 01c48165-c6ae-43c7-ade0-fb3a5ca08ee2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}